Izzy Young collection, 1942-2015
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Manuscripts, ca. 1942-2015
  - Subseries C: Topical binders
    - New correspondence, 2008, 1 item (Box 65)
      Printed email correspondence and a couple of handwritten correspondence. Includes correspondence with Suze Rotolo. Also includes article about Izzy Young written in Hebrew.
    - NOW, then!; NY City, ca. 1992-2011, 2 items (Box 66)
      Includes correspondence.
    - Phil Ochs, ca. 1968-2003, 1 item (Box 67)
      Includes articles about Phil Ochs, as well Och's song lyrics and a typed interview with Izzy Young and Ochs.
    - Outside world, 1990-1991, 1990-1992, 1 item (Box 68)
      Includes business cards, as well as correspondence. Correspondents include Marc Silber, Joe Hickerson, Dick Weissman, and Kate Rinzler.
    - Photos; Poesi, IGY (Israel Goodman Young), 1962-2013, 2 items (Box 69)
      Photos removed and placed into Series III. Includes an article about Izzy Young in Swedish, correspondence (including a letter from Oscar Brand), other ephemera, and writings by Young (including interviews with Bob Dylan).
    - Poetry USA; Poetry II Izzy, ca. 1961-2014, 2 items (Box 70)
      Includes clippings and articles about poets in English and Swedish. Significant portion are about Allen Ginsberg. Poetry II Izzy binder includes printed poems, fliers, and an article about Izzy Young in Swedish.
    - Press clips from Israel G. Young archives, press scrapbooks, etc., 1963-1971, 1 item (Box 71)
      Includes printouts of correspondence, fliers, newspaper articles, and press releases.
    - Pressklipp, 1985-1989, 1 item (Box 72)
      Clippings and articles about musicians and music promoters (mostly in English).
    - Pressklipp, 1987, 1 item (Box 73)
      Clippings and articles about musicians and music promoters (mostly in Swedish).
    - Pressklipp, 1988, 1 item (Box 74)
      Clippings and articles about musicians and related topics (mostly in Swedish). Includes clippings from article about Izzy Young.
    - Pressklipp, 1989, 1 item (Box 75)
      Clippings and articles about musicians and related topics (in Swedish).
    - Pressklipp, 1990, 1 item (Box 76)
      Clippings and articles about music, dance, and related topics (in Swedish).
    - Pressklipp, 1990-1992, 1 item (Box 77)
      Clippings and articles about musicians and related topics (mostly in English).
    - Pressklipp, 1991, 1 item (Box 78)
    - Pressklipp pa Svenska, 1991, 1 item (Box 79)
      Clippings and articles about musicians and related topics (in Swedish). Includes article about Izzy Young.
    - Pressklipp, 1994, 1 item (Box 80)
      Clippings and articles about music, dance, and related topics (in English and Swedish).
    - Pressklipp, 1995, 1 item (Box 81)
      Clippings and articles about musicians and related topics (in English and Swedish).
    - Pressklipp, 1996, 1 item (Box 82)
    - Pressklipp, 1997, 1 item (Box 83)
    - Pressklipp, 1998, 1 item (Box 84)
    - Pressklipp, 2000, 1 item (Box 85)
    - Research and long articles; Information, miscellaneous, ca. 2003, 1 item (Box 86)
      Articles about folk music and musicians, including articles about Alan Lomax and Woody Guthrie.
    - Richard Reuss interview, Izzy Young, 1965, 1 item (Box 87)
      Typed interview transcript with Izzy Young and Richard Reuss.
    - Dick Reuss, Dexter, Bear Family Records, 1965-1992, 1 item (Box 88)
      Includes "Folk Scene Diary Summer 1965" by Richard Reuss, interview with Izzy Young and Herb Dexter, writeup about Bear Family record set, and two articles by Ronald Cohen and Dave Samuelson.
    - Right of Return; Ryan, Pinko, Gahr; Rani, Cath, Sarah, 2001, 2009, 2 items (Box 89)
      Printed email correspondence in Swedish and English about the Right of Return (Israel). Right of Return; Ryan, Pinko, Gahr; Rani, Cath, Sarah binder includes correspondence with Rani Singh, Earle Pinko, Andy Schwartz, and others.
    - Pete Seeger II; Pete Seeger and Izzy, 2004-2013, 2 items (Box 90)
      Articles about Pete Seeger. Pete Seeger and Izzy binder includes correspondence and postcards between Izzy Young and Pete Seeger.
    - Pete Seeger, [Woody] Guthrie, Weavers, 1964-1999, 1 item (Box 91)
      Articles and clippings about Pete Seeger and Woody Guthrie. One photograph of Seeger removed and placed in Series III.
    - Seeger-Young letters and Harold Leventhal, 1966-2008, 1 item (Box 92)
      Primarily includes correspondence between Izzy Young and Pete Seeger. Includes postcards from Pete Seeger. Also includes letters to Harold Leventhal. One photograph of Seeger removed and placed in Series III.
    - Harry Smith, 1966-2001, 1 item (Box 93)
      Includes correspondence between Izzy Young and Allen Ginsberg, as well as Izzy Young and Greil Marcus.
    - Smith Barney; South Africa copyright, Paul Simon, Wimoweh, 2000-2004, 2 items (Box 94)
      Statements for Izzy Young and Folklore Centrum from Salomon Smith Barney. South Africa copyright, Paul Simon, Wimoweh binder includes correspondence with Pete Seeger, Mark Moss, and articles about Seeger's recording of "Wimoweh" and Paul Simon's recording of Graceland.
    - Svensk Folkmusik; Suze, 1977-2009, 2 items (Box 95)
      Written on binder spine: Svenska folkets Musik? Om Izzy Youngs arbete I sverige. Includes articles (in Swedish) about folk music in Sweden. Suze binder includes printed email correspondence between Izzy Young and Suze Rotolo.
    - The Telegraph; Dylan interview; Semneby article; Correspondence; Unclassified articles, journals, 1977-1998, 2 items (Box 96)
      Includes correspondence about Jan Semneby's article about Izzy Young in the Telegraph. Also includes typed Bob Dylan interview with Izzy Young from 1961. Unclassified articles, journals binder includes writings by and about Izzy Young. Includes retyped journal entry from 1962. Also includes correspondence.
    - WIP, UNESCO copyright; Israel G. Young Folklore Center correspondence as found in the Richard Reuss folklore archives at Indiana University, May 1991, 1959-1969, 1997, 2 items (Box 97)
      Report from UNESCO-WIPO World Forum on the Protection of Folklore from April 8-10, 1997. Note from Izzy Young to Mark Moss written on cover page. Israel G. Young Folklore Center correspondence as found in the Richard Reuss folklore archives at Indiana University, May 1991 binder includes printed correspondence between Izzy Young and correspondents, such as Pete and Toshi Seeger, Barbara Dane, Margot Mayo, Archie Green, Guy Carawan, and Manny Greenhill.
    - Untitled binder, 1957-2013, 1 folder (Box-folder 133/1)
      Business cards, publishing agreements, Folklore Center fliers and advertisements, writings, and correspondence.
    - Untitled binder, 1961-1974, 1 item (Box 98)
      Clippings and articles primarily about Bob Dylan and the release of his albums (in English).
    - Untitled binders, 1976-1986, 2 items (Box 99)
      Clippings and articles primarily about Bob Dylan (in English and Swedish), and about musicians and related topics. Includes articles about Izzy Young.
    - Untitled binder, 2001-2003, 1 item (Box 100)
      Invoices from the Folklore Centrum (in Swedish).
    - 2005 Mail, 2004-2005, 1 item (Box 101)
      Printed email correspondence with correspondents, including Rani Singh, Nathan and Robert Salsburg, Todd Harvey, and Elijah Wald. Photographs were removed from binder and placed in Series III.
    - Untitled binder, ca. 1958-1995, 2008, 2 items (Box 102)
      Clippings and articles primarily about Bob Dylan (in English and Swedish). Clippings, correspondence, and writings by Izzy Young. Includes 1958 quote by Young from the Village Voice. Includes article about Young in Swedish.
  - Subseries D: Correspondence
    - Ronald Cohen, ca. 2006-2007 (Box-folder 133/2)
      Letters between Izzy Young and history professor Ronald D. Cohen.
    - Parents, ca. 1944-1970 (Box-folder 103/1)
      Letters between Izzy Young and his parents, Pola and Philip Young. Includes a letter from Philip Young to Moses Asch, 1965.
    - Philomene Grandin, ca. 1993-2001 (Box-folder 103/2-3)
      Letters from Izzy Young's daughter.
    - Margi H., 1960-1962 (Box-folder 103/4)
    - J. Edgar Hoover, 1965 (Box-folder 103/5)
    - Pete and Toshi Seeger, 1977-1998 (Box-folder 103/6)
    - Shirley, ca. 1957-1958 (Box-folder 103/7-8)
    - Laura Tennen, ca. 1961-1964 (Box-folder 103/9-11)
    - Booker T. White, 1966 (Box-folder 103/12)
    - General correspondence, ca. 1962-2013 (Box-folder 103/13)
      Includes correspondence with Ralph Rinzler, Theodore Bikel, Dick Waterman, and Mark Moss.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1962-1966 (Box-folder 103/14)
      Includes correspondence regarding Sing Out! and Folk Music magazines.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1962-2006 (Box-folder 133/3)
      Includes correspondence with Ronald Cohen, Peter K. Siegel, Richard Reuss, and others.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1961-2014 (Box-folder 103/15)
      Includes correspondence with Rani Singh, Lou Gottlieb, and Lou Killen.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1960-1998 (Box-folder 103/16)
      Includes correspondence with Deborah Sperberg, and other personal correspondence.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1965-2007 (Box-folder 104/1)
      Includes correspondence (primarily printed emails) with Jeff Rosen, Suze Rotolo, and others.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1965-2014 (Box-folder 104/2)
      Includes correspondence with Irwin Silber, Ron Cohen, and Charles Seeger.
    - General correspondence, 1986 (Box-folder 104/3)
      Includes correspondence with Harold Leventhal, Richard Reuss, and Pat Sky.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1966-2011 (Box-folder 104/4)
      Includes correspondence with Pete and Toshi Seeger, John Cohen, Scott Barretta, and others.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1974-2004 (Box-folder 104/5)
      Includes correspondence with Rani Singh, Ida Cohen, and others.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1974-2004 (Box-folder 104/5)
    - General correspondence, ca. 1983-2008 (Box-folder 133/4)
      Includes correspondence with Ronald Cohen, Lucy Neville, Jerome Epstein, and others.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1991-2013 (Box-folder 104/7)
      Includes correspondence with Benjamin Filene, Guy Logsdon, and Annabel Faraday.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1986-2011 (Box-folder 104/8)
      Includes correspondence with JoAnne Reuss, Dave Van Ronk, and Marc Silber.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1986 (Box-folder 104/9)
    - General correspondence, ca. 1962-2009 (Box-folder 104/10)
      Includes correspondence with Pete and Toshi Seeger, Ralph and Kate Rinzler, and Laura Tennen.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1983-2010 (Box-folder 104/11)
      Includes correspondence with Scott Barretta, Ron Cohen, and Suze Rotolo.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1977-2004 (Box-folder 105/1)
      Includes correspondence with Lou Gottlieb, Sis and Gordon Friesen, and Scott Barretta.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1963-2008 (Box-folder 105/2)
      Includes postcards.
    - General correspondence, ca. 1977-2012 (Box-folder 105/3)
  - Subseries E: Ephemera
    Includes folk and folklore programs, newsletters, announcements, and concert fliers. Includes items of note for the Folklore Center.
    - Folklore programs, catalogs, newsletters, and announcements, ca. 1963-2010 (Box-folder 105/4-9)
      Includes a 1959 insert from Sing Out! Magazine, Harold Leventhal announcements, issues of Skandia Folkdance Society Newsletter, New York Pinewoods Folk Music Club newsletters, Freight and Salvage calendars.
    - Folklore programs, catalogs, newsletters, and announcements, ca. 1960-2004 (Box-folder 106/1-9)
      Includes folk music newsletters and magazines. Includes Folklore Center catalogs, newsletters, fliers, and programs for concerts and poetry readings.
    - Folklore programs, catalogs, newsletters, and announcements, ca. 1958-2014 (Box-folder 107/1-8)
      Includes Harold Leventhal announcements, Folknik newsletters, and Folklore Society of Greater Washington newsletters.
    - Folklore programs, catalogs, newsletters, and announcements, ca. 1965-1986 (Box-folder 133/5)
      Includes issues of Folklin' Around, Village Scene, and Stray Notes.
    - Folklore programs, catalogs, newsletters, and announcements, ca. 1960-2016 (Box-folder 133/6)
      Includes 2016 Nobel Prize program, letter from the Newport Folk Foundation, folk music festival and camp programs, pages from scrapbooks, and correspondence.
    - Folk festivals and Folklore Center programs, ca. 1965-1968 (Box-folder 107/9)
    - Folklore Center readings, 1968 (Box-folder 107/10)
      Programs for Folklore Center poetry readings.
    - Folklore Centrum programs, ca. 1970-1980 (Box-folder 108/1-2)
    - Folklore Centrum ephemera, business cards, ca. 2000-2007 (Box-folder 108/3)
    - Swedish and European music programs, ca. 1977-2011 (Box-folder 108/4)
    - Swedish language music programs, ca. 1992 (Box-folder 108/5)
    - Swedish Square Dance Club programs, ca. 1980-1995 (Box-folder 108/6)
    - Programs: Sassafras, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 108/7)
      "The Journal of the People's Music Network for Songs of Freedom and Struggle."
    - Concert fliers, ca. 1957-1991 (Box-folder 108/8-12)
      Includes "Folklore Center Presents" concert fliers, Friends of Old Time Music flier, Sunset Park flier, Harold Leventhal Presents concert flier, and fliers for many folk concerts and festivals.
    - Concert fliers, ca. 1962-1966 (Box-folder 133/7)
      Includes "Folklore Center Presents" concert fliers and fliers for other folk concerts and festivals.
    - Concert fliers, ca. 1962-2000 (Box-folder 109/1-2)
      Includes "Folklore Center Presents" poetry reading fliers, 1962 flier for a Hedy West concert, and Reverend Gary Davis, Bob Dylan concert fliers.
    - Drawing of Pete Seeger, 1976 (Box-folder 109/3)
      Drawing by Per Rosenberg.
    - Bob Dylan fanzines, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 109/4)
      Magazines about Bob Dylan from the Folklore Centrum collection.
    - Bob Dylan fanzines, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 109/5)
    - Bob Dylan fanzines - Zimmerman Blues, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 109/6)
      Three issues of Zimmerman Blues, a magazine about Bob Dylan, from the Folklore Centrum collection.
    - Bob Dylan's first New York Concert flier, Carnegie Hall, 1961-11-04 (Box-folder 109/7)
      Program for "Folklore Center Presents Bob Dylan in his first New York Concert," at Carnegie Chapter Hall. Includes biography of Dylan and description of Folklore Center. Also includes an inscription from Izzy Young from October 2015 to the Library of Congress.
    - Broadside, #1-50, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 109/8-10)
      Issues of Broadside, The National Topical Magazine, including sheet music for topical songs.
    - Broadside, #1-50, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 110/1)
    - Broadside, #51-90, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 110/2-5)
    - Broadside, #91-187, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 110/6)
    - Broadside, #91-187, 1970-1987 (Box-folder 111/1-3)
    - Original Folklore Center logo, ca. 1960 (Box-folder 111/4)
      Note from Izzy Young that first preliminary sketch of Folklore Center logo was from 1959 scrapbook.
    - Robert Zimmerman songbook, ca. 1972-1985 (Box-folder 111/5)
      Book of Bob Dylan song lyrics from the Folklore Centrum collection. Note from Izzy Young on front cover: "made in Sweden. A very good illegal collection, including 'poems.'"
    - Izzy Young's high school diploma, 1942 (Box-folder 111/6)
      Diploma from the Board of Education of the City of New York.
    - Jewish topics, Klezmer music, ca. 1990-1999 (Box-folder 111/7)
      Includes programs for klezmer concerts, camps, and festivals.
    - Folklore Center patent, 1963 (Box-folder 112/1)
      Folklore Center patent from the United States Patent Office.
    - Musikens Makt magazine, 1974 (Box-folder 112/2)
      Three issues of Swedish Music magazines.
    - Folklore Center programs, ca. 1965-1966 (Box-folder 112/3)
      Programs for poetry readings at the Folklore Center.
    - Folklore programs, catalogs, newsletters, and announcements, ca. 1964-1988 (Box-folder 112/4)
    - Correspondence and poems, 1963, 1966, 2000 (Box-folder 112/5)
      Correspondence with Izzy Young, and two poems.
  - Subseries F: Newspaper articles and clippings
    Includes programs, catalogs, newsletters, concert fliers, and announcements.
    - Articles about Allen Ginsberg, ca. 1990-1998 (Box-folder 113/1)
    - Articles and clippings about Pete Seeger, ca. 1965-2014 (Box-folder 113/2)
    - Folk music articles and clippings, ca. 1957-2014 (Box-folder 113/3-12)
      Includes articles and clippings about folk musicians, festivals, various musical styles, the release of musical recordings, Izzy Young, and Civil Rights activism.
    - Folk music articles and clippings, ca. 1998-2000 (Box-folder 114/1-6)
      Articles in Swedish, French, and English.
    - Folk music articles and clippings, ca. 1962-2000 (Box-folder 115/1-3)
      Includes folk music articles, clippings, and press releases. Includes articles about Izzy Young. Articles in Swedish, English, and Hebrew.
  - Subseries G: Writings
    Includes Izzy Young journal entries, writings, and poems, as well as some writings and poems by others.
    - Izzy Young's writings and journal entries, ca. 1959-2010 (Box-folder 115/4-9)
      Includes typed journal entries (including from 1961 discussing Bob Dylan), the transcript of an interview with Young, "Jews in Folk Music" essay, and sheet music to song about Young wrote about his daughter, Philomene.
    - Izzy Young's writings and journal entries, ca. 1964-2015 (Box-folder 133/9-11)
      Includes poem from the opening of the Folklore Center, drafts of articles, and entries from Young's notebooks and journals.
    - Interviews, journals, misc., ca. 1965-1991 (Box-folder 133/8)
      Includes typed journal entries, scrapbook entries, and transcribed interviews.
    - Moses Asch interview, 1970 (Box-folder 133/9)
      Interview trascriptions. "First raw copy of Moe Asch interview with Israel Young, June 25, 1970. The interview as typed is partially edited, leaving out that which obviously would be left out of the final interview in type."
    - Poetry by Robert Reinhold, 1967 (Box-folder 116/1)
    - Selected poetry, ca. 1957-2015 (Box-folder 116/2-8)
      Includes influential poems and songs, including a 1957 poem didacatory on the Opening of the Folklore Center, and poems by Langston Hughes and Allen Ginsberg. Includes poems by Izzy Young.
  - Subseries H: Administrative
    - Passports, ca. 1969-1980 (Box-folder 117/1)
      Izzy Young's expired passport books.
    - Passports, ca. 1980-2006 (Box-folder 117/2)
    - Blood donor certificate cards, ca. 1950-1955 (Box-folder 117/3)
    - New York City voting card, 1965 (Box-folder 117/4)
    - Philomene Grandin vaccination certificate, ca. 1974-1975 (Box-folder 117/5)
      Izzy Young's daughter's vaccination form in Swedish.
    - Banking papers and correspondence with Salomon Smith Barney, ca. 1980-1999 (Box-folder 117/6)
- Series II: Sound recordings, ca. 1960-1975
  Includes recordings of concerts promoted by Izzy Young, concerts at the Folklore Center and other venues, and radio programs. Digitization is complete for some of the sound recordings.
  - Sound recording documentation (folder 1), ca. 1963-1980 (Box-folder 117/7)
    Documentation found with open reel tape boxes. Includes information on sound recording contents, song titles, and dates. Organized by "sr" number, which corresponds to sound recording numbering system.
  - Sound recording documentation (folder 2), ca. 1963-1980, ca. 1964-1990 (Box-folder 133/13)
    Documentation found with open reel tape boxes and cassettes. Includes information on sound recording contents, song titles, and dates. Organized by "sr" number, which correspondends to sound recording numbering system.
  - Unidentified content, 1970, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR001)
    Written on original tape box: "Folk 4. Folk 70."
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR002)
  - Poetry performance, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR003)
    Includes John Ashbury, Sam Abrams, Ted Berrigan, Jerome Rothenberg, and David Antin.
  - Unidentified content, 1970, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR004)
  - Sam Loveman, 1967, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR005)
    Written on original tape box: "Hermaphrodite."
  - Young Traditions, 1968, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR006)
    Includes Sea shanties, "Bold reginal," "The two magicians," "John Barley Corn," "The husband man and the serving man," and "Watercress-o."
  - Art Rosenbaum tape, 1969-04-09, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR007)
    Written on original tape box: "Recorded Wednesday night, April 9, 1969, at Washington Square Methodist Church."
  - Karl Dallas, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR008)
    Written on original tape box: "On the British scene radio show interview."
  - Kirkpatrick, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR009)
    Written on original tape box: "Tape 1, Part 1."
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR010)
    Written on original tape box: "Latin America."
  - Poetry performance, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR011)
  - The Young Tradition, 1968, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR012)
    Written on original tape box: "Recorded by Mike Asch."
  - Unidentified content in Swedish, ca. 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR013)
    Content list in Swedish in Accompanying documentation for sound recordings folder.
  - Israeli folk music, 1967, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR014)
    Written on original tape box: "King's Hotel, Jerusalem."
  - "Young Tradition" program, 1968-11-18, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR015)
  - Leslie Ferguson playing in Washington Square, 1968-05-26, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR016)
  - Joe Ceravolo and Larry Fagin, 1968-05-12, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR017)
  - "Folk Festival, #2", 1961, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR018)
  - Catherine, ca. 1965-1975, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR019)
    Written on original tape box: "Music to make Catherine strong by."
  - "Folk music, CBC-2", 1960-06-16, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR020)
  - Hedy West, ca. 1965-1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR021)
  - Unidentified content, ca. 1965-1972, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR022)
  - "Radio show. Folk I.", 1970-03-28, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR023)
  - Hedy West, 1968-11-30, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR024)
    Hedy West at the Folklore Center.
  - Tom Paley, 1969-02-12, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR025)
  - A.L. Lloyd lecture, Philadelphia, 1968-03-28, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR026)
  - Folkmusik PA Stockholms Stadsmuseum, 1969-12-01, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR027)
    Contents and performer list located in box 117, folder 7.
  - Harry E. Smith interview, 1968-04-30, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR028)
  - Stagnant Eagle and the Strangebirds, 1965, 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/040: SR029)